Normal subtitle line one.
Line with italic and bold tags.
Missing index number here.
Invalid timestamp format - missing milliseconds.
No spaces around arrow.
Text after empty block.
This is a very long subtitle line that exceeds typical length limits. It contains multiple sentences to test how the parser handles extremely long text content that might wrap across multiple lines in the actual video player display. Some subtitle files may contain overly verbose translations or descriptions that result in unusually long text blocks like this one.
Colored text with underline.
Line with special chars: &  " '
Multi-line subtitle
that spans across
three lines.
Tab	character	in	text.
Trailing spaces after text.
Leading spaces before text.
Last subtitle without final newline